fasttechbuzz.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

**FastTechBuzz.com respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of www.fasttechbuzz.com.

**Credit card details**

www.fasttechbuzz.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on www.[fasttechbuzz](http://www.fasttechbuzz.com/).com

**External Sites**

www.fasttechbuzz.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies  **

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows www.fasttechbuzz.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and www.fasttechbuzz.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to www.[fasttechbuzz](http://www.fasttechbuzz.com/).com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through www.fasttechbuzz.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

               We also use third party advertisements on www.[fasttechbuzz](http://www.fasttechbuzz.com/).com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure

I will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.Data like your email address will not be made visible on the site, unless you choose to display it.  
For any other information email to WebMaster.

Thanks,

[Srinu Ipathy](https://plus.google.com/u/0/109626100725102934571?rel=author).
